<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://yangfan2001.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>Fan Yang Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-07-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://yangfan2001.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>Fan Yang Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://yangfan2001.github.io/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[关于23fall申请季的总结]]></title>
        <id>总结</id>
        <link href="https://yangfan2001.github.io/blog/总结"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[23fall的申请就这么结束了，作为陆本申请mscs的学生，深刻的感受到了mscs项目的申请难度。]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>23fall的申请就这么结束了，作为陆本申请mscs的学生，深刻的感受到了mscs项目的申请难度。</p><p>同时我也被签证深深伤害了。
附上了我的Study Plan:</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="study-plan">Study Plan<a class="hash-link" href="#study-plan" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h2><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="research-area-of-interest-and-major">Research Area of Interest and Major<a class="hash-link" href="#research-area-of-interest-and-major" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><p>I am pursuing a Master of Science in Computer Science at New York University. This is a course-based program which I intend to complete within a span of two years.</p><p>The MSCS program at New York University offers a wide array of concentrations. I have chosen to focus my studies on data visualization, front-end development, and website development.</p><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="advisor-or-potential-advisor">Advisor or Potential Advisor<a class="hash-link" href="#advisor-or-potential-advisor" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><p>Megan Charlton and the program director is Yi-Jen Chiang</p><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="program-description">Program Description<a class="hash-link" href="#program-description" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><p>The Master of Science in Computer Science (MSCS) program at New York University's Tandon School of Engineering offers a highly adaptive curriculum that allows students to shape the degree around their interests. The program provides a fundamental grounding in computer science while offering a wide range of electives. Students can tailor the program to their professional goals in areas such as data science, information visualization, machine learning and AI, graphics, game engineering, responsible computing, algorithms, and web search technology.</p><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="course-list">Course List<a class="hash-link" href="#course-list" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><p>CS-GY 6003 Foundations of Computer Science</p><p>CS-GY 6033 Design and Analysis of Algorithms I</p><p>CS-GY 6043 Design and Analysis of Algorithms II</p><p>CS-GY 6053 Foundation of Data Science</p><p>CS-GY 6063 Software Engineering I</p><p>CS-GY 6083 Principles of Database Systems</p><p>CS-GY 6093 Advanced Database Systems</p><p>CS-GY 6133 Computer Architecture I</p><p>CS-GY 6233 Introduction to Operating Systems</p><p>CS-GY 6243 Operating Systems II</p><p>CS-GY 6253 Distributed Operating Systems</p><p>CS-GY 6313 Information Visualization</p><p>CS-GY 6323 Large-Scale Visual Analytics</p><p>CS-GY 6373 Programming Languages</p><p>CS-GY 6413 Compiler Design and Construction</p><p>CS-GY 6513 Big Data</p><p>CS-GY 6533 Interactive Computer Graphics</p><p>CS-GY 6543 Human Computer Interaction</p><p>CS-GY 6553 Game Design</p><p>CS-GY 6573 Penetration Testing and Vulnerability Analysis</p><p>CS-GY 6613 Artificial Intelligence I</p><p>CS-GY 6643 Computer Vision</p><p>CS-GY 6703 Computational Geometry</p><p>CS-GY 6753 Theory of Computation</p><p>CS-GY 6763 Algorithmic Machine Learning and Data Science</p><p>CS-GY 6803 Information Systems Security Engineering and Management</p><p>CS-GY 6813 Information, Security and Privacy</p><p>CS-GY 6823 Network Security</p><p>CS-GY 6843 Computer Networking</p><p>CS-GY 6903 Applied Cryptography</p><p>CS-GY 6913 Web Search Engines</p><p>CS-GY 6923 Machine Learning</p><p>CS-GY 6943 Artificial Intelligence for Games</p><p>CS-GY 6953 Deep Learning</p><p>CS-GY 6963 Digital Forensics</p><p>CS-GY 9053 Special Topics in Computer Science: Intro to Java</p><p>CS-GY 9163 Application Security</p><p>CS-GY 9223 Selected Topics in Computer Science</p><p>CS-GY 9963 Advanced Project in Computer Science</p><p>CS-GY 997X M.S. Thesis in Computer Science</p><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="funding">Funding<a class="hash-link" href="#funding" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><p>My financial sponsor will be my brother, Wei Yang, and in addition, I have been awarded an annual scholarship of $4,000 from New York University.</p><h4 class="anchor anchorWithStickyNavbar_LWe7" id="career-object--future-plan">Career Object &amp; Future Plan<a class="hash-link" href="#career-object--future-plan" title="Direct link to heading">​</a></h4><p>In the immediate two years, I will be fully committed to pursuing my Master's degree in Computer Science at New York University's Tandon School of Engineering. During this time, I plan to specialize in front-end technologies, data visualization, and web development and production, areas that I believe are critical to the digital and technology landscape.My studies at NYU Tandon will provide a solid theoretical and practical foundation in these areas. I am particularly looking forward to the hands-on learning experiences that will allow me to apply the theories I learn in class to real-world problems, enhancing my problem-solving and technical skills.</p><p>Upon completion of my studies in the United States, I intend to return to my home country, China, specifically to Shanghai, where I plan to seek opportunities in the tech industry. I am keen to work in an environment that is at the forefront of technological innovation, and Shanghai, being one of the technology hubs in China, is the ideal place for me to do so. In the short term, I see myself as a front-end developer, leveraging the skills and knowledge that I will have gained from my time at NYU Tandon. I am excited about the prospect of contributing to a company’s success through creating intuitive, user-friendly interfaces and improving overall user experience. In the long term, I aspire to become a product manager. I believe that this role will allow me to use my technical knowledge and my understanding of user needs to oversee the overall design and control of software products. It is a role that requires strategic thinking, leadership, and a deep understanding of the technology market, all of which I am committed to developing throughout my career.</p><p>I believe that this plan will allow me to contribute significantly to the technology industry in China, and I am eager to bring back the valuable knowledge and experiences I will gain from studying in the United States.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Fan Yang</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/yangfan2001</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="hello" term="hello"/>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://yangfan2001.github.io/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2023-01-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello World!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello World!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Fan Yang</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/yangfan2001</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="hello" term="hello"/>
    </entry>
</feed>